ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- SSS, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  report on labor dramatics, Round Robins, list of motion pictures for Workers' groups, report of Carolina conference on workers' education held at Highlander Folk School
- SSS, 1939-1943 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  reports, correspondence with L. L. McLaren, The Springboard, including news of alumnae, list of motion pictures, and re visual education and conference in graphic arts
- SSS, 1942-1944 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  correspondence with Brownie Lee Jones, director, annual reports, appeal for toys for children of textile strikers, draft of proposed "Reader" for workers, report of interracial projects at the Hampton Institute, cooperation with local unions
- SSS, 1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  B. L. Jones, recruiting, interracial session conducted in Washington, 1947, annual reports and report to Board, "What is the SSS doing that the labor Movement cannot do as well for itself?"
- SSS, Annual reports, 1940-1941 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Committees (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Vineyard Shore Summer School, fliers (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Wisconsin Summer Institutes, 1931-1933 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Wisconsin School for Workers, 1932-1939 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  summary of Workers'
- WSW, Ernest Schwarztrauber, 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  re accepting Black students, reports, correspondence with Alice Shoemaker
- WSW, annual reports, prospectus, aluman newsletter, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- WSW, newsletters, prospectus, annual reports, articles about WSW, 1943-1948 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- WSW, alumnae letters, 1932-1935 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- WSW, fliers, articles, and texts (Box 27, Folder 24)
- WSW, fliers, articles, and texts (Box 27, Folder 25)
- BMSS, minutes of Board meetings, Mary R. M. Griffiths to faculty, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- BMSS, reports, 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  on Marxian study group, conference re social insurance, on health (by Elizabeth L. Otey,) and science and dramatics
- BMSS, 1934-1938 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  songbook, reports and minutes of Board of Directors' meetings, Helen Hill's The Effect of the BMSS as Measured in the Activities of its Students
- BMSS, report of factfinding committee of BMSS alumnae, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- BMSS, minutes of the Board meeting, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- BMSS, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  will and obituary of M.Carey Thomas, minutes of Board meetings, prospectus, mimeographed reports: Hewes- Beecher, "Outline of Discussion of the Problems of American workers," "The Non-working time of Industrial Women Workers, "a mock radio program, "We Are America," "Building and Singing, "a dramatic productionworkers," "The Non-working time of Industrial Women Workers, "a mock radio program, "We Are America," "Building and Singing, "a dramatic production
- Board minutes and fliers, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Board minutes and fliers, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Hudson Shore Labor School (HSLS) formerly BMSS, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  John Casswell Smith's, Each Man is an Island account of race relations at HSLS, poems by Hilda W. Smith, musical revues, bulletins and other pamphlets
- HSLS, includes funding sources, 1939-1948 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- HSLS, reports and correspondence with acting director Mabel Leslie, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- HSLS, 1941-1945 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  reports, announcements, correspondence with Marie Algor, director, Caroline Ware's "Labor and Democracy in the Home: an interchange of views between household workers and household employers
- HSLS, kit and yearbook containing source material, 1949-1952 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- American-Scandinavian Foundation, 1938-1951 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- American-Scandinavian Foundation, 1938-1951 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- American-Scandinavian Foundation, 1938-1951 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Committee on occupied area (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Committee on International Education Exchange (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Fulbright Scholarships in adult and workers' education (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Fulbright Scholarships in adult and workers' education (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Institute of International Exchange (Box 29, Folder 8)
- International Exchange of Students (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Ruskin College Labor Scholarships, 1947-1951 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Ruskin College Labor Scholarships, 1947-1951 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Ruskin College Labor Scholarships, 1947-1951 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Denmark (Box 29, Folder 13)
- England (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Sweden (Box 29, Folder 15)
- South, Central America, Mexico, and other scholarships (Box 29, Folder 16)
- South, Central America, Mexico, and other scholarships (Box 29, Folder 17)
- U.S. Dept of Labor, Exchange of Workers' programs (Box 29, Folder 18)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor, Women's Bureau (Box 29, Folder 19)
- U.S. Dept of Labor, Office of International Labor Affairs (Box 29, Folder 20)
- U.S. Dept. of State (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Dr. Harold Taylor, President of Sarah Lawrence College, re funds for foreign scholarships (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Oliver Peterson, U.S. embassy in Sweden, 1949-1951 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Names and addresses of contacts in unions and workers' education useful for arranging tours of foreign visitors (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "What's happening to Labor and what lies ahead", 1940 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "What's happening to Labor and what lies ahead", 1940 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "What's happening to Labor and what lies ahead", 1940 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "What's happening to Labor and what lies ahead", 1940 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "What's happening to Labor and what lies ahead", 1940 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "What's happening to Labor and what lies ahead", 1940 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Midwest conference, Waukegan, Ill., "Labor's Membership Participation", 1941 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., "Workers education in the war and post-war economy", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "Unions and the Community" also includes Minorities workshop, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Midwest conference, Racine, Wise., "Workers' education in the post-war economy", 1944 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- Registration cards (Box 30, Folder 47)
- Registration cards (Box 30, Folder 48)
- Registration cards (Box 30, Folder 49)
- Registration cards (Box 30, Folder 50)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How Labor must serve the Labor movement today", 1945 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "How can workers education advance labor's political and economic objectives?", 1946 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Midwest conference, Highland Park, Ill., 1947 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- Midwest conference, Milwaukee, "Social Security, Whose Responsibility?", 1949 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 51)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 54)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 55)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 56)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 57)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 58)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 59)
- Midwest conference, Chicago, "International Affairs", 1950 (Box 31, Folder 60)
- Conference of professionals in Workers' education, Chicago, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 61)
- Conference of professionals in Workers' education, Chicago, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 62)
- Conference of professionals in Workers' education, Chicago, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 63)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 64)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 65)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Northwest farmers and Workers' education conference, registration cards, 1946-1950 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- New. Jersey Minority Project, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  Marie Algor's reports describing cooperation with CIO in eradicating discrimination against Blacks and other racial minorities,. in unions, through education
- New. Jersey Minority Project, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- New. Jersey Minority Project, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- New. Jersey Minority Project, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- New. Jersey Minority Project, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- New. Jersey Minority Project, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- New Jersey Minority Project, ALES Board planning (Box 32, Folder 37)
- New Jersey Minority Project, ALES Board planning (Box 32, Folder 38)
- New Jersey Minority Project, conference at Butler N. J. (Box 32, Folder 39)
- New Jersey Minority Project, statistics, memos, and minutes (Box 32, Folder 40)
- New Jersey Minority Project, N. J. CIO committee to abolish discrimination, 1947-1948 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- New Jersey Minority Project, Marie Algor's correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- New Jersey Minority Project, Virginia Wicks, Marie Algor, reports and correspondence, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- New Jersey Minority Project, Memos on union work and other contacts, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- New Jersey Minority Project, N. J. CIO correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- St. Louis Minority Project, 1944-1949 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  background material includes Eleanor Emerson's "Proposal for developing Labor's resources in dealing with anti-semitism and discrimination against Blacks," and Eleanor Copenhaver Anderson's article in Labor and Nation, surveys and studies on attitudes to Blacks in St. Louis
- St. Louis Minority Project, 1944-1949 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- St. Louis Minority Project, 1944-1949 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- St. Louis Minority Project, 1944-1949 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- St. Louis Minority Project, correspondence of Annetta Dieckmann and Coit (Box 33, Folder 5)
- St. Louis Minority Project, correspondence of Annetta Dieckmann and Coit (Box 33, Folder 6)
- St. Louis Minority Project, correspondence of Annetta Dieckmann and Coit (Box 33, Folder 7)
- St. Louis Minority Project, correspondence of Annetta Dieckmann and Coit (Box 33, Folder 8)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 9)
  on contacts and interviews with community and union officials on attitudes to racial discrimination
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 10)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 11)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 12)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 13)
- St. Louis Minority Project, American Jewish committee, 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  includes Mrs. Pearl Willen and Mr. Sigman
- St. Louis Minority Project, American Jewish committee, 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- St. Louis Minority Project, Teamsters' Local 688, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- St. Louis Minority Project, Teamsters' Local 688, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports, personnel, contact with Textile Workers', 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports, personnel, contact with Textile Workers', 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports, personnel, contact with Textile Workers', 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports, personnel, contact with Textile Workers', 1948-1949 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 22)
  on history of S. Louis labor movement and publicity
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports (Box 33, Folder 23)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports of Anetta Dieckmann Paul Swaity, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- St. Louis Minority Project, reports of Anetta Dieckmann Paul Swaity, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- St. Louis Minority Project, Missouri State Council CID reports, 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- St. Louis Minority project, Central Trades and Labor Union, minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- St. Louis Minority Project, Marie Algor's reports (Box 34, Folder 5)
- St. Louis Minority Project, cooperation with White Collar-Workshops, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- St. Louis Minority Project, organization of project, 1947-1949 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- St. Louis Minority Project, organization of project, 1947-1949 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- St. Louis Minority Project, organization of project, 1947-1949 (Box 34, Folder 9)